Then I'm gonna stop at a pet store
and get licked by puppies.
(Leonard:)-Sheldon, I need to talk to you.
-All right, my friend.
(Sheldon:)Would you like some cholermus?
(Leonard:)-Some what?
-Cholermus.
(Sheldon:)It's a traditional Swiss breakfast dish.
(Sheldon:)I'm preparing my gastrointestinal system
for the exotic cuisine of Switzerland.
(Leonard:)-You're not going to Switzerland.
-Oh, but I am.
(Sheldon:)Didn't Penny tell you the good news?
(Leonard:)You went behind my back to guilt her
into letting you go instead of her.
(Sheldon:)Yes, that good news.
Forget it. I was the one invited,
I get to decide who goes with me.
(Leonard:)And it's Penny, not you.
(Sheldon:)Howard, could you lower the lights?
I have a short PowerPoint presentation.
(Leonard:)I don't need to see your presentation.
This discussion is over.
Well, that's a somewhat
ambiguous response. Am I going or not?
(Leonard:)Sheldon, at this point...
(Leonard:)...I would go by myself
before I would take you.
(Sheldon:)-Really?
-Yeah, really.
(Raj:)Well, then.
You leave me no alternative.